https://www.crime-scene-investigator.net/privacypolicy.html

Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Crime Scene Investigator Network website (http://www.crime-scene-investigator.net) and Crime Scene Resources and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Crime Scene Resources include the Crime Scene Investigator Network and http://www.crime-scene-investigator.net. The Crime Scene Resources website is an educational and information site. By using the Crime Scene Resources website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Crime Scene Resources may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. Crime Scene Resources may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your age. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Crime Scene Resources. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Crime Scene Resources website.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Crime Scene Resources' public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.
Crime Scene Resources encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Crime Scene Resources so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Crime Scene Resources is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Crime Scene Resources website.
Use of your Personal Information
Crime Scene Resources collects and uses your personal information to operate its websites and deliver the services you have requested. Crime Scene Resources may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Crime Scene Resources and its affiliates. Crime Scene Resources may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Crime Scene Resources does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Crime Scene Resources may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is transferred to the third party. Crime Scene Resources may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Crime Scene Resources, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Crime Scene Resources may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Crime Scene Resources, in order to determine what Crime Scene Resources services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Crime Scene Resources to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Crime Scene Resources will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Crime Scene Resources or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Crime Scene Resources; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Crime Scene Resources, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Crime Scene Resources website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Crime Scene Resources pages, or register with Crime Scene Resources site or services, a cookie helps Crime Scene Resources to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Crime Scene Resources website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Crime Scene Resources features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Crime Scene Resources services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Crime Scene Resources secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.
Children Under Thirteen
Crime Scene Resources does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Opt-Out and Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Crime Scene Resources by contacting us here:
Unsubscribe form for Newsletters and/or Job Posting Alert emails.
OR
Email: unsubscribe@crimesceneresources.com
Changes to this Statement
Crime Scene Resources will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Crime Scene Resources encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Crime Scene Resources is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Crime Scene Resources welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Crime Scene Resources has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Crime Scene Resources at:
Crime Scene Resources, Inc.
PO Box 1043
34190 Harvest Way
Wildomar, California 92595-1043
Email Address: info@crimesceneresources.com
Effective as of April 10, 2013
Updated November 7, 2019
Tweets by CSInetwork
"Follow" to Receive Job Alerts
Follow @CSInetwork
CLEARANCE SALE25% OFF and FREE SHIPPING!
Shirts from ForensicWear.com
CLEARANCE SALE25% OFF and FREE SHIPPING!With coupon code "CLEARANCE" at checkout. Limited to styles and sizes on hand. Orders are shipped to USA addresses only.
